BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 17) 6178/017
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- RR Maintenance of Way - Louisville and Nashville, 1921-1927 (Box 21, Folder 47)
  1921, 1923, 1924, 1927
- RR Maintenance of Way - Illinois Central, 1922-1923 (Box 21, Folder 48)
- RR Maintenance of Way - Great Northern, 1921 (Box 21, Folder 49)
- RR Maintenance of Way - Grand Trunk, 1921-1923 (Box 21, Folder 50)
- RR Employees - National, 1916 (Box 21, Folder 51)
- RR Passenger Train Porters - Great Northern, 1921 (Box 21, Folder 52)
- RR Shopmen - Seaboard Air Line, 1911 (Box 21, Folder 53)
- RR Shopmen - Wheeling and Lake Erie, 1912 (Box 21, Folder 54)
- RR Shopmen - Wabash, 1912-1914 (Box 21, Folder 55)
- RR Shopmen - Great Northern, 1903-1917 (Box 21, Folder 56)
  1903, 1905, 1913, 1916, 1917
- RR Shopmen - Rio Grande Western, 1915 (Box 21, Folder 57)
- RR Shopmen - Missouri, Kansas, Texas, 1922 (Box 21, Folder 58)
- RR Shopmen - Great Northern, 1922 (Box 21, Folder 59)
- RR Shopmen - Northern Pacific, 1903-1917 (Box 21, Folder 60)
  1903, 1916, 1917
- RR Shopmen - Hocking Valley, 1917 (Box 21, Folder 61)
- RR Shopmen - Northern Pacific, 1903-1918 (Box 21, Folder 62)
  1903, 1916, 1917, 1918
- RR Shopmen - Illinois Central, 1922 (Box 21, Folder 63)
- RR Shopmen - Yazoo and Mississippi Valley, 1921 (Box 21, Folder 64)
- RR Shopmen - Great Northern, 1917 (Box 21, Folder 65)
- RR Shopmen - Minneapolis and St. Louis, 1913-1917 (Box 21, Folder 66)
  1913, 1916, 1917
- RR Shopmen - Missouri, Kansas, Texas, 1927 (Box 21, Folder 67)
- RR Shopmen - Minneapolis and St. Louis, 1922 (Box 21, Folder 68)
- RR Shopmen - New Orleans, LA, 1923 (Box 21, Folder 69)
- RR Shopmen - Great Northern, 1927 (Box 21, Folder 70)
- RR Shopmen - New York, New Haven and Hartford, 1914-1917 (Box 21, Folder 71)
  1914, 1916, 1917
- RR Shopmen - St. Louis and San Francisco, 1913 (Box 21, Folder 72)
- RR Shopmen - Chicago and Erie, 1923-1927 (Box 21, Folder 73)
- RR Shopmen - Florida East Coast, 1921 (Box 21, Folder 74)
- RR Shopmen - Hocking Valley, 1922 (Box 21, Folder 75)
- RR Shopmen - Gulf Coast Lines, 1922 (Box 21, Folder 76)
- RR Shopmen - Ft. Smith and Western, 1913 (Box 21, Folder 77)
- RR Shopmen - Missouri, Kansas, Texas, 1904-1916 (Box 21, Folder 78)
  1904, 1905, 1916
- RR Shopmen - Lake Erie and Western, 1904 (Box 21, Folder 79)
- RR Shopmen - Toledo, OH, 1905 (Box 21, Folder 80)
- RR Shopmen - Central of GA, 1905 (Box 21, Folder 81)
- RR Shopmen - Chesapeake and Ohio, 1904 (Box 21, Folder 82)
- RR Shopmen - Chicago and Eastern Illinois, 1903 (Box 21, Folder 83)
- RR Shopmen - Illinois Central, 1922 (Box 21, Folder 84)
- RR Shopmen - Davenport, IA (Box 21, Folder 85)
- RR Shopmen - Southern, 1905-1911 (Box 21, Folder 86)
- RR Shopmen - Chicago and Great Western, 1905 (Box 21, Folder 87)
- RR Shopmen - Chicago and North Western, 1904 (Box 21, Folder 88)
- RR Shopmen - Delaware and Hudson, 1926 (Box 21, Folder 89)
- RR Shopmen - St. Louis, 1913-1917 (Box 21, Folder 90)
- RR Shopmen - Philadelphia and Reading, 1922 (Box 21, Folder 91)
- RR Shopmen - Norfolk and Western Railway, 1906 (Box 21, Folder 92)
- RR Shopmen - Minnesota and International, 1921 (Box 21, Folder 93)
- RR Shopmen - New York, NY, 1922-1923 (Box 21, Folder 94)
- RR Shopmen - Nashville, Chattanooga and St. Louis, 1922-1924 (Box 21, Folder 95)
- RR Shopmen - Chicago, Milwaukee and St. Paul, 1905-1917 (Box 21, Folder 96)
  1905, 1913, 1916, 1917
- RR Shopmen - Erie, PA, 1905 (Box 21, Folder 97)
- RR Shopmen - Boston and Maine, 1913-1920 (Box 21, Folder 98)
  1913, 1916, 1917, 1920
- RR Shopmen - Chicago, Indianapolis, Louisville, 1917 (Box 21, Folder 99)
- RR Shopmen - Chicago, Milwaukee and St. Paul, 1916 (Box 21, Folder 100)
- RR Shopmen - Chicago, Milwaukee and St. Paul, 1905-1917 (Box 21, Folder 101)
- RR Shopmen - New York City, Chicago, St. Louis, 1917 (Box 21, Folder 102)
- RR Shopmen - CCC and St. Louis, 1906 (Box 21, Folder 103)
- RR Shopmen - Chicago, St. Paul, Minneapolis, Omaha, 1905-1917 (Box 21, Folder 104)
- RR Shopmen - Cincinnati, Hamilton and Dayton, 1911 (Box 21, Folder 105)
- RR Shopmen - Boston and Maine, 1917 (Box 21, Folder 106)
- RR Shopmen - Chicago, Milwaukee and St. Paul, 1917 (Box 21, Folder 107)
- RR Shopmen - Erie, PA, 1904 (Box 21, Folder 108)
- RR Shopmen - Minneapolis and St. Paul, 1917 (Box 21, Folder 109)
- RR Shopmen - Missouri Pacific, 1913-1917 (Box 21, Folder 110)
- RR Shopmen - Minneapolis and St. Louis, 1913 (Box 21, Folder 111)
- RR Shopmen - Denver and Rio Grande Western, 1916 (Box 21, Folder 112)
- RR Shopmen - Missouri, Kansas, Texas, 1917 (Box 21, Folder 113)
- RR Shopmen - Great Northern, 1923 (Box 21, Folder 114)
- RR Shopmen - Wheeling and Lake Erie, 1922 (Box 21, Folder 115)
- RR Shopmen - Philadelphia and Reading, 1921 (Box 21, Folder 116)
- RR Shopmen - Colorado and Southern, 1922 (Box 21, Folder 117)
- RR Shopmen - Pittsburgh and Lake Erie, 1923-1928 (Box 21, Folder 118)
  1923, 1928
- RR Clerks, Freight Handlers - Southern, 1921 (Box 21, Folder 119)
- RR Clerical and Station Employees - Southern Pacific, 1922 (Box 21, Folder 120)
- RR Shopmen - Missouri Pacific, 1903 (Box 21, Folder 121)
- RR Shopmen - New York, NY, 1922 (Box 21, Folder 122)
- RR Shopmen - Pere Marquette, 1923-1927 (Box 21, Folder 123)
- RR Shopmen - Boston and Maine, 1905-1906 (Box 21, Folder 124)
- RR Shopmen - Maine Central, 1921-1927 (Box 21, Folder 125)
- RR Shopmen - Chicago, Milwaukee and St. Paul, 1917-1918 (Box 21, Folder 126)
- RR Shopmen - Central NJ, 1918 (Box 21, Folder 127)
- RR Shopmen - Delaware and Hudson, 1926 (Box 21, Folder 128)
- RR Shopmen - Chicago, Milwaukee and St. Paul, 1917 (Box 21, Folder 129)
- RR Shopmen - Pittsburgh and Lake Erie, 1926 (Box 21, Folder 130)
- RR Shopmen - Philadelphia and Reading, 1921 (Box 21, Folder 131)
- RR Shopmen - Eastern Pennsylvania, 1924 (Box 21, Folder 132)
- RR Shopmen - New York, New Haven and Hartford, 1922 (Box 21, Folder 133)
- RR Shopmen - Great Northern, 1922-1926 (Box 21, Folder 134)
- RR Shopmen - Kansas City Southern, 1913 (Box 21, Folder 135)
- RR Shopmen - New York, New Haven and Hartford, 1921 (Box 21, Folder 136)
- RR Shopmen - Chicago and North Western, 1917 (Box 21, Folder 137)
- RR Shopmen - Seaboard Air Line, 1905-1909 (Box 21, Folder 138)
  1905, 1909
- RR Shopmen - Illinois Central, 1904-1922 (Box 21, Folder 139)
  1904, 1905, 1922
- RR Shopmen - Pittsburgh and Lake Erie, 1926 (Box 21, Folder 140)
- RR Shopmen - Atlantic Coast Lines, 1906 (Box 21, Folder 141)
- RR Shopmen - Minneapolis and St. Louis, 1921 (Box 21, Folder 142)
- RR Shopmen - New York, Chicago, St. Louis, 1922 (Box 21, Folder 143)
- RR Shopmen - Grand Trunk, 1922 (Box 21, Folder 144)
- RR Shopmen - Missouri Pacific, 1922-1926 (Box 21, Folder 145)
- RR Shopmen - Norfolk and Western Railway, 1905-1906 (Box 21, Folder 146)
- RR Shopmen - New York, New Haven and Hartford, 1907-1916 (Box 21, Folder 147)
- RR Shopmen - Missouri Pacific, 1903-1917 (Box 21, Folder 148)
  1903, 1904, 1910, 1913, 1916, 1917
- RR Shopmen - Minneapolis and St. Louis, 1906-1917 (Box 21, Folder 149)
  1906, 1910, 1913, 1916, 1917
- RR Shopmen - Denver and Rio Grande Western, 1916-1917 (Box 21, Folder 150)
- RR Shopmen - Evansville and Terre Haute, 1905 (Box 21, Folder 151)
- RR Shopmen - Erie, PA, 1905 (Box 21, Folder 152)
- RR Shopmen - N/A, 1919 (Box 21, Folder 153)
- RR Shopmen - Cincinnati, Indianapolis, Western, 1916-1921 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- RR Shopmen - N/A, 1911 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- RR Shopmen - Chicago, St. Paul, Minneapolis, Omaha, 1905-1917 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  1905, 1910, 1913, 1915, 1917
- RR Shopmen - Cincinnati, 1916 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- RR Shopmen - Duluth, Winnipeg and Pacific, 1925 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- RR Shopmen - Chicago, Rock Island and Pacific, 1922-1927 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  1922, 1925, 1926, 1927
- RR Shopmen - Chicago, Milwaukee and St. Paul, 1916-1917 (Box 22, Folder 8)
- RR Shopmen - Duluth, South Shore and Atlantic, 1927 (Box 22, Folder 9)
- RR Shopmen - Denver and Rio Grande Western, 1922-1926 (Box 22, Folder 10)
- RR Shopmen - Richmond, VA, 1906 (Box 22, Folder 11)
- RR Shopmen - Chesapeake and Ohio, 1905 (Box 22, Folder 12)
- RR Shopmen - Central of GA, 1912 (Box 22, Folder 13)
- RR Shopmen - Danville and Western, 1922 (Box 22, Folder 14)
- RR Shopmen - Denver and Rio Grande Western, 1911-1918 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  1911, 1916, 1918
- RR Shopmen - Delaware, Lackawanna and Western, 1922 (Box 22, Folder 16)
- RR Shopmen - Salt Lake City, UT, 1917 (Box 22, Folder 17)
- RR Shopmen - Delaware and Hudson, 1926 (Box 22, Folder 18)
- RR Shopmen - Chicago and North Western, 1904-1905 (Box 22, Folder 19)
- RR Shopmen - Chicago Great Western, 1905-1924 (Box 22, Folder 20)
- RR Shopmen - Chicago, Burlington and Quincy, 1922-1926 (Box 22, Folder 21)
- RR Shopmen - Chicago and Western Indiana, 1916-1927 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  1916, 1927
- RR Shopmen - Lehigh Valley, 1922 (Box 22, Folder 23)
- RR Shopmen - Northwestern Pacific, 1922 (Box 22, Folder 24)
- RR Shopmen - Baltimore and Ohio, 1905-1917 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  1905, 1911, 1916, 1917
- RR Administration - N/A, 1919 (Box 22, Folder 26)
- RR Marine Repair Shops - Long Island Railroad, 1922 (Box 22, Folder 27)
- RR Maintenance of Equipment - Long Island Railroad, 1922 (Box 22, Folder 28)
- RR Shopmen - Seaboard Air Line, 1921 (Box 22, Folder 29)
- RR Shopmen - Southern, 1905-1916 (Box 22, Folder 30)
  1905, 1911, 1916
- RR Shopmen - Colorado and Southern, 1922 (Box 22, Folder 31)
- RR Shopmen - Chicago and Rock Island, 1922 (Box 22, Folder 32)
- RR Shopmen - Chicago Junction, 1916 (Box 22, Folder 33)
- RR Shopmen - Duluth and Iron Range, 1905-1913 (Box 22, Folder 34)
  1905, 1913
- RR Maintenance of Equipment - Long Island Railroad, 1922 (Box 22, Folder 35)
- RR Association - Louisville and Nashville, 1922 (Box 22, Folder 36)
- RR Shopmen - Maine Central, 1917 (Box 22, Folder 37)
- RR Shopmen - Lake Shore and Michigan Southern, 1903-1906 (Box 22, Folder 38)
- RR Association - Lake Erie and Western, 1922 (Box 22, Folder 39)
- RR Shopmen - Kentucky and Indiana, 1914 (Box 22, Folder 40)
- RR Shopmen - St. Louis and San Francisco, 1913 (Box 22, Folder 41)
- RR Shopmen - Chicago, Burlington and Quincy, 1917 (Box 22, Folder 42)
- RR Shopmen - Chicago and North Western, 1916-1917 (Box 22, Folder 43)
- RR Shopmen - Denver and Rio Grande Western, 1916-1917 (Box 22, Folder 44)
- RR Shopmen - Delaware and Hudson, 1926 (Box 22, Folder 45)
- RR Shopmen - Denver and Rio Grande Western, 1911-1919 (Box 22, Folder 46)
  1911, 1916, 1917, 1919
- RR Shopmen - Boston and Maine, 1922 (Box 22, Folder 47)
- RR Shopmen - Chicago, Rock Island and Pacific, 1916 (Box 22, Folder 48)
- RR Shopmen - Colorado and Southern, 1913-1917 (Box 22, Folder 49)
- RR Shopmen - Cleveland, Cincinnati, Chicago and St. Louis, 1917 (Box 22, Folder 50)
- RR Shopmen - Chicago, St. Paul, Minneapolis, Omaha, 1910-1917 (Box 22, Folder 51)
  1910, 1913, 1916, 1917
- RR Shopmen - Chicago, Milwaukee and St. Paul, 1921-1926 (Box 22, Folder 52)
- RR Shopmen - Minneapolis and International, 1923 (Box 22, Folder 53)
- RR Shopmen - Chicago, Milwaukee and St. Paul, 1913-1916 (Box 22, Folder 54)
- RR Shopmen - Chicago and Alton, 1913 (Box 22, Folder 55)
- RR Shopmen - Denver and Salt Lake City, 1913-1916 (Box 22, Folder 56)
- RR Shopmen - Chicago, Rock Island and Pacific, 1906 (Box 22, Folder 57)
- RR Shopmen - Illinois Central, 1922 (Box 22, Folder 58)
- RR Shopmen - Missouri, Kansas and Texas, 1917 (Box 22, Folder 59)
- RR Shopmen - Southern, 1905 (Box 22, Folder 60)
- RR Shopmen - Louisiana and Arkansas, 1926 (Box 22, Folder 61)
- RR Shopmen - Seaboard Air Line, 1923 (Box 22, Folder 62)
- RR Shopmen - Texas Pacific, 1906-1913 (Box 22, Folder 63)
  1906, 1913
- RR Shopmen - Buffalo, Rochester, Pittsburgh, 1916-1917 (Box 22, Folder 64)
- RR Shopmen - Chesapeake and Ohio, 1912-1922 (Box 22, Folder 65)
  1912, 1922
- RR Shopmen - Baltimore and Ohio, 1923-1926 (Box 22, Folder 66)
- RR Shopmen - Chicago and Eastern Illinois, 1913 (Box 22, Folder 67)
- RR Shopmen - Chicago and Alton, 1922-1925 (Box 22, Folder 68)
- RR Shopmen - Hocking Valley, 1924-1926 (Box 22, Folder 69)
- RR Shopmen - Kansas City, Mexico and Orient, 1914-1920 (Box 22, Folder 70)
- RR Shopmen - Missouri, Kansas and Texas, 1908-1916 (Box 22, Folder 71)
  1908, 1913, 1916
- RR Shopmen - Missouri Pacific, 1913-1917 (Box 22, Folder 72)
- RR Shopmen - Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe, 1922-1925 (Box 22, Folder 73)
- RR Shopmen - Cleveland, Cincinnati, Chicago and St. Louis, 1923 (Box 22, Folder 74)
- RR Shopmen - Kansas City Southern, 1913 (Box 22, Folder 75)
- RR Shopmen - St. Louis and San Francisco, 1913-1917 (Box 22, Folder 76)
- RR Shopmen - Duluth, South Shore and Atlantic, 1921 (Box 22, Folder 77)
- RR Shopmen - Southern, 1921-1926 (Box 22, Folder 78)
- RR Shopmen - Great Northern, 1922-1923 (Box 22, Folder 79)
- RR Shopmen - Norfolk and Western Railway, 1922 (Box 22, Folder 80)
- RR Shopmen - Northern Pacific, 1922 (Box 22, Folder 81)
- RR Shopmen - Minneapolis, St. Paul and Sault Ste. Marie, 1913-1917 (Box 22, Folder 82)
- RR Shopmen - Atlantic Coast Lines, 1917 (Box 22, Folder 83)
- RR Shopmen - Ann Arbor, 1927 (Box 22, Folder 84)
- RR Shopmen - Union Pacific, 1922-1926 (Box 22, Folder 85)
- RR Shopmen - Illinois Central, 1922 (Box 22, Folder 86)
- RR Shopmen - Missouri, Kansas and Texas, 1916 (Box 22, Folder 87)
- RR Shopmen - Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe, 1892 (Box 22, Folder 88)
- RR Shopmen - Tennessee Central, 1922 (Box 22, Folder 89)
- RR Shopmen - New York, New Haven and Hartford, 1922 (Box 22, Folder 90)
- RR Shopmen - Richmond, Fredericksburg and Potomac, 1922 (Box 22, Folder 91)
- RR Shopmen - Missouri Pacific, 1913-1916 (Box 22, Folder 92)
- RR Shopmen - Chicago, Minneapolis, St. Paul, 1917 (Box 22, Folder 93)
- RR Shopmen - Cleveland, Cincinnati, Chicago and St. Louis, 1913 (Box 22, Folder 94)
- RR Shopmen - Chicago and North Western, 1915-1917 (Box 22, Folder 95)
- RR Shopmen - Norfolk and Western Railway, 1920 (Box 22, Folder 96)
- RR Shopmen - Missouri Pacific, 1913-1917 (Box 22, Folder 97)
  1913, 1916,1917
- RR Shopmen - Michigan Central, 1924 (Box 22, Folder 98)
- RR Shopmen - Escanaba and Lake Superior, 1927 (Box 22, Folder 99)
- RR Shopmen - Chicago, St. Paul, Minneapolis, Omaha, 1917-1920 (Box 22, Folder 100)
- RR Shopmen - Chicago and Eastern Illinois, 1922 (Box 22, Folder 101)
- RR Shopmen - Southern Pacific, 1904 (Box 22, Folder 102)
- RR Shopmen - Mobile and Ohio, 1905 (Box 22, Folder 103)
- RR Shopmen - Pennsylvania, 1921 (Box 22, Folder 104)
- RR Shopmen - Pennsylvania, 1923 (Box 22, Folder 105)
- RR Shopmen - Norfolk and Western Railway, 1922 (Box 22, Folder 106)
- RR Shopmen - Great Northern, 1910-1917 (Box 22, Folder 107)
- RR Shopmen - New York, Ontario and Western, 1914 (Box 22, Folder 108)
- RR Shopmen - Minneapolis and St. Louis, 1918 (Box 22, Folder 109)
- RR Shopmen - New York Central, 1922 (Box 22, Folder 110)
- RR Shopmen - Pennsylvania, 1923 (Box 22, Folder 111)
- RR Shopmen - Missouri Pacific, 1922 (Box 22, Folder 112)
- RR Shopmen - Mobile and Ohio, 1927 (Box 22, Folder 113)
- RR Shopmen - East Broad Tap, 1919 (Box 22, Folder 114)
- RR Shopmen - Minneapolis, St. Paul and Sault Ste. Marie, 1918 (Box 22, Folder 115)
- RR Shopmen - Atlantic Coast Lines, 1922-1926 (Box 22, Folder 116)
- RR Shopmen - Eastern Pennsylvania, 1923 (Box 22, Folder 117)
- RR Shopmen - Pennsylvania and Cincinnati, 1922 (Box 22, Folder 118)
- RR Shopmen - Puerto Rico, 1916 (Box 22, Folder 119)
- RR Shopmen - Utah, 1922 (Box 22, Folder 120)
- RR Shopmen - Western Maryland, 1922 (Box 22, Folder 121)
- RR Shopmen - Nevada Northern, 1918 (Box 22, Folder 122)
- RR Shopmen - Cleveland, Cincinnati, Chicago and St. Louis, 1922 (Box 22, Folder 123)
- RR Shopmen - West Virginia, 1906 (Box 22, Folder 124)
- RR Shopmen - Central Vermont, 1923 (Box 22, Folder 125)
- RR Shopmen - Chicago Great Western, 1923 (Box 22, Folder 126)
- RR Shopmen - Chicago, 1916 (Box 22, Folder 127)
- RR Shopmen - St. Louis, 1917 (Box 22, Folder 128)
- RR Supervisors of Mechanics - Great Northern (Box 22, Folder 129)
- RR Shopmen - Louisville and Nashville, 1922-1926 (Box 22, Folder 130)
- RR Shopmen - Missouri Pacific, 1904-1916 (Box 22, Folder 131)
  1904, 1910, 1913, 1916
- RR Shopmen - New York Central, 1906 (Box 22, Folder 132)
- RR Shopmen - Minneapolis and St. Louis, 1911-1917 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  1911, 1913, 1916, 1917
- RR Shopmen - Missouri, Kansas and Texas, 1923 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- RR Shopmen - Michigan Central, 1905 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- RR Shopmen - Central Vermont, 1923 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- RR Shopmen - Chicago, Milwaukee and St. Paul, 1917 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- RR Shopmen - Buffalo, Rochester, Pittsburgh, 1921 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- RR Shopmen - Delaware and Hudson, 1926 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- RR Shopmen - Chicago and North Western, 1923-1927 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- RR Shopmen - St. Louis, 1927 (Box 23, Folder 9)
- RR Shopmen - Trinity and Brazos Valley, 1922 (Box 23, Folder 10)
- RR Shopmen - Toledo, OH, 1927 (Box 23, Folder 11)
- RR Shopmen - Toledo, Peoria and Western, 1927 (Box 23, Folder 12)
- RR Shopmen - Pittsburgh and West Virginia, 1922 (Box 23, Folder 13)
- RR Shopmen - San Antonio, Uvalde and Gulf, 1923 (Box 23, Folder 14)
- RR Shopmen - New York, NY, 1922 (Box 23, Folder 15)
- RR Shopmen - Gulf, Mobile and Northern, 1922 (Box 23, Folder 16)
- RR Shopmen - Great Northern, 1917 (Box 23, Folder 17)
- RR Shopmen - Southern Pacific, 1922 (Box 23, Folder 18)
- RR Station Forces - Philadelphia and Reading, 1921 (Box 23, Folder 19)
- RR Shopmen - St. Louis, 1916-1917 (Box 23, Folder 20)
- RR Shopmen - Chicago, Milwaukee and St. Paul, 1918 (Box 23, Folder 21)
- RR Shopmen - Pittsburgh and Lake Erie, 1923 (Box 23, Folder 22)
- RR Shopmen - St. Louis, 1921 (Box 23, Folder 23)
- RR Shopmen - Kentucky and Indiana, 1917 (Box 23, Folder 24)
- RR Shopmen - Kansas City, 1916 (Box 23, Folder 25)
- RR Shopmen - Northern Pacific, 1920 (Box 23, Folder 26)
- RR Shopmen - Norfolk Southern (Box 23, Folder 27)
- RR Shopmen - New York, 1923 (Box 23, Folder 28)
- RR Shopmen - Southern Pacific, 1922-1926 (Box 23, Folder 29)
- RR Shopmen - Long Island Railroad, 1923 (Box 23, Folder 30)
- RR Shopmen - Illinois Central, 1922 (Box 23, Folder 31)
- RR Shopmen - Spokane, Portland and Seattle, 1925 (Box 23, Folder 32)
- RR Shopmen - Chicago, Milwaukee and St. Paul, 1903-1905 (Box 23, Folder 33)
- RR Shopmen - New Orleans and Northeastern, 1905 (Box 23, Folder 34)
- RR Shopmen - Minneapolis, St. Paul and Sault Ste. Marie, 1913-1917 (Box 23, Folder 35)
- RR Shopmen - St. Louis, 1923 (Box 23, Folder 36)
- RR Shopmen - St. Louis and San Francisco, 1904-1922 (Box 23, Folder 37)
  1904, 1906, 1922
- RR Shopmen - Ft. Worth and Denver City, 1925 (Box 23, Folder 38)
- RR Shopmen - Missouri, Kansas and Texas, 1903-1916 (Box 23, Folder 39)
  1903, 1910, 1913, 1916
- RR Shopmen - Maine Central, 1922-1928 (Box 23, Folder 40)
  1922, 1926, 1928
- RR Shopmen - Western Pacific, 1923 (Box 23, Folder 41)
- RR Shopmen - Wabash, 1922-1924 (Box 23, Folder 42)
- RR Shopmen - Northern Pacific, 1903-1918 (Box 23, Folder 43)
  1903, 1905, 1910, 1913, 1916, 1917, 1918
- RR Shopmen - Oregon, 1917 (Box 23, Folder 44)
- RR Shopmen - Seaboard Air Line, 1911 (Box 23, Folder 45)
- RR Shopmen - Missouri, Kansas and Texas, 1916 (Box 23, Folder 46)
- RR Shopmen - St. Louis, Brownsville and Mexico, 1923 (Box 23, Folder 47)
- RR Shopmen - Northern Pacific, 1922-1923 (Box 23, Folder 48)
- RR Shopmen - Missouri Pacific, 1921 (Box 23, Folder 49)
- RR Firemen - Portland, 1924 (Box 23, Folder 50)
- RR Switchmen - Lehigh Valley, 1922 (Box 23, Folder 51)
- RR Switchmen - Chicago, Rock Island and Pacific, 1922 (Box 23, Folder 52)
- RR Switchmen - Chicago, Milwaukee and St. Paul, 1903 (Box 23, Folder 53)
- RR Switchmen - Detroit and Toledo, 1920 (Box 23, Folder 54)
- RR Shopmen - Union Pacific, 1927 (Box 23, Folder 55)
- RR Signalmen - Los Angeles and Salt Lake City, 1927 (Box 23, Folder 56)
- RR Signalmen - Louisville and Nashville, 1922 (Box 23, Folder 57)
- RR Signalmen - Buffalo, Rochester, Pittsburgh, 1923 (Box 23, Folder 58)
- RR Signalmen - Canadian National, 1924 (Box 23, Folder 59)
- RR Signalmen - Central of GA, 1921 (Box 23, Folder 60)
- RR Signalmen - Atlantic Coast Lines, 1922 (Box 23, Folder 61)
- RR Signalmen - Baltimore and Ohio, 1922 (Box 23, Folder 62)
- RR Signalmen - Chicago, 1927 (Box 23, Folder 63)
- RR Signalmen - New York, NY, 1922 (Box 23, Folder 64)
- RR Signalmen - New York City and St. Louis, 1921 (Box 23, Folder 65)
- RR Signalmen - Lake Erie and Western, 1922-1923 (Box 23, Folder 66)
- RR Signalmen - Norfolk and Western Railway, 1923 (Box 23, Folder 67)
- RR Signalmen - Union Pacific, 1922 (Box 23, Folder 68)
- RR Signalmen - Northern Pacific, 1923 (Box 23, Folder 69)
- RR Parked Car Employees - Minneapolis, St. Paul and Sault Ste. Marie, 1924 (Box 23, Folder 70)
- RR Supervisors of Mechanics - Baltimore and Ohio, 1921 (Box 23, Folder 71)
- RR Signalmen - Illinois Central, 1922 (Box 23, Folder 72)
- RR Signalmen - Michigan Central, 1923 (Box 23, Folder 73)
- RR Signalmen - Minneapolis, St. Paul and Sault Ste. Marie, 1921 (Box 23, Folder 74)
- RR Signalmen - Missouri Pacific, 1922 (Box 23, Folder 75)
- RR Signalmen - Lehigh Valley, 1923-1924 (Box 23, Folder 76)
- RR Signalmen - Chicago and Alton, 1922 (Box 23, Folder 77)
- RR Signalmen - Central of NJ, 1922 (Box 23, Folder 78)
- RR Signalmen - Missouri, Kansas and Texas, 1922 (Box 23, Folder 79)
- RR Signalmen - Chicago, Milwaukee and St. Paul, 1922 (Box 23, Folder 80)
- RR Signalmen - Chicago and North Western, 1922 (Box 23, Folder 81)
- RR Signalmen - Cleveland, Cincinnati, Chicago and St. Louis, 1922 (Box 23, Folder 82)
- RR Signalmen - Delaware, Lackawanna and Western, 1923 (Box 23, Folder 83)
- RR Signalmen - Chicago and Erie, 1923-1925 (Box 23, Folder 84)
- RR Signalmen - Great Northern, 1921 (Box 23, Folder 85)
- RR Signalmen - Chicago, Burlington and Quincy, 1922 (Box 23, Folder 86)
- RR Signalmen - Chicago and Eastern Illinois, 1922 (Box 23, Folder 87)
- RR Signalmen - N/A, 1920 (Box 23, Folder 88)
- RR Signalmen - Yazoo and Mississippi Valley, 1922 (Box 23, Folder 89)
- RR Signalmen - Oregon, 1927 (Box 23, Folder 90)
- RR Signalmen - Philadelphia and Reading, 1921 (Box 23, Folder 91)
- RR Signalmen - Southern, 1921-1926 (Box 23, Folder 92)
- RR Signalmen - South Pacific Lines, 1922-1926 (Box 23, Folder 93)
- RR Switchmen - New York, NY, 1921-1923 (Box 23, Folder 94)
- RR Switchmen - Pere Marquette, 1906 (Box 23, Folder 95)
- RR Switchmen - Michigan Central, 1920 (Box 23, Folder 96)
- RR Switchmen - Maine Central, 1920 (Box 23, Folder 97)
- RR Switchmen - Chicago and Eastern Illinois, 1919 (Box 23, Folder 98)
- RR Switchmen - N/A, 1905 (Box 23, Folder 99)
- RR Switchmen - Northern Pacific, 1905 (Box 23, Folder 100)
- RR Switchmen - N/A (Box 23, Folder 101)
- RR Switchmen - Texas and New Orleans, 1903 (Box 23, Folder 102)
- RR Telegraphers - Missouri Pacific, 1904-1923 (Box 23, Folder 103)
  1904, 1923
- RR Telegraphers - Cincinnati, Hamilton and Dayton, 1905 (Box 23, Folder 104)
- RR Telegraphers - Cleveland, Cincinnati, Chicago and St. Louis, 1924 (Box 23, Folder 105)
- RR Telegraphers - Colorado and Southern, 1919-1923 (Box 23, Folder 106)
- RR Telegraphers - Denver and Rio Grande Western, 1919-1924 (Box 23, Folder 107)
- RR Telegraphers - N/A (Box 23, Folder 108)
- RR Telegraphers - Richmond, Fredericksburg and Potomac, 1906-1918 (Box 23, Folder 109)
  1906, 1918
- RR Telegraphers - Rutland, 1922-1927 (Box 23, Folder 110)
- RR Telegraphers - St. Louis and San Francisco, 1906 (Box 23, Folder 111)
- RR Telegraphers - Seaboard Air Line, 1924 (Box 23, Folder 112)
- RR Telegraphers - Pittsburgh and Lake Erie, 1916-1928 (Box 23, Folder 113)
  1916, 1924, 1928
- RR Telegraphers - Pennsylvania, 1921-1922 (Box 23, Folder 114)